&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：总结本课程的内容。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Wrapping things up for this course.
总而言之，我可以简单地说，如果出于任何疯狂的原因，你决定
In summary, I can simply say, if for whatever crazy reason you've decided to
让[笑]你的职业生涯此刻以JavaScript为中心，
make [LAUGH] your career centered around JavaScript at this moment,
了解您的JavaScript不是很有意义吗？
doesn't it make sense to know your JavaScript?
更好奇不是更有意义吗，
Doesn't it make sense to be more curious,
问更多关于它的问题，想知道代码为什么工作，
to ask more questions about it, to want to know why the code works,
这样当它坏了的时候你有机会试着去修理它吗？
so that you have any chance of trying to fix it when it breaks?
认真对待不是更有意义吗
Doesn't it make more sense to take it seriously, and
每隔一段时间读一读规范，并理解，并有一个心智模型，和
read the spec every once in a while and understand, and have a mental model, and
最重要的是，通过对该工具的了解，交流您的想法和
most importantly through the understanding of that tool communicate your ideas and
你的意图更有效。
your intent more effectively.
非常感谢你倾听我对JavaScript的想法。
Thanks very much for listening to my thoughts on JavaScript.
我希望在你前进的过程中，你会继续这种好奇心
I hope that as you go forward, you will continue that curiosity and
那种好奇心，那些问题的人。
that inquisitiveness, those asking questions.
记住，我有很多材料要添加
Remember that I have lots of materials out there to add to and
支持这项特殊的研究。
support this particular study.
You Don‘t Know JS图书系列确实是一个很好的资源。
The You Don't Know JS book series is really a great resource.
所有六本书都可以在GitHub上阅读。
All six books can be read up on GitHub.
具体地说，本课程的三本书将是范围和闭包
Specifically, the three books from this course would be the Scope and Closures
书，这和对象原型书，和类型和语法书。
book, the This and Object Prototypes book, and the Types and Grammar book.
因此，当您深入挖掘这些主题时，请使用这些学习指南
So use those as your dig deeper into these topics study guides
从球场之外。
from beyond the course.
非常感谢。
Thanks very much.
我很感激你倾听这些想法。
I appreciate you listening to these thoughts.
&gt；&gt；观众：[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Audience: [APPLAUSE]